A Guide to the Virginia Newspaper Collection, 1861-1992
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Boxes 11, 13, 14, 16: Richmond (Box 11, Box 13, Box 14, Box 16)
  - Daily Dispatch (Richmond Dispatch), Richmond, VA
    - 05/09/1861, XIX, 106 (Box 16)
    - 05/10/1861, XIX, 107 (Box 16)
    - 05/11/1861, XIX, 108 (Box 16)
    - 05/13/1861, XIX, 109 (Box 16)
    - 05/14/1861, XIX, 110 (Box 16)
    - 05/15/1861, XIX, 111 (Box 16)
    - 05/16/1861, XIX, 112 (Box 16)
    - 05/17/1861, XIX, 113 (Box 16)
    - 05/18/1861, XIX, 114 (Box 16)
    - 05/20/1861, XIX, 115 (Box 16)
    - 05/21/1861, XIX, 116 (Box 16)
    - 05/22/1861, XIX, 117 (Box 16)
    - 05/23/1861, XIX, 118 (Box 16)
    - 05/24/1861, XIX, 119 (Box 16)
    - 05/25/1861, XIX, 120 (Box 16)
    - 05/27/1861, XIX, 121 (Box 16)
    - 05/28/1861, XIX, 122 (Box 16)
    - 05/29/1861, XIX, 123 (Box 16)
    - 05/30/1861, XIX, 124 (Box 16)
    - 05/31/1861, XIX, 125 (Box 16)
    - 06/01/1861, XIX, 126 (Box 16)
    - 06/03/1861, XIX, 127 (Box 16)
    - 06/04/1861, XIX, 128 (Box 16)
    - 06/05/1861, XIX, 129 (Box 16)
    - 06/06/1861, XIX, 130 (Box 16)
    - 06/07/1861, XIX, 131 (Box 16)
    - 06/08/1861, XIX, 132 (Box 16)
    - 06/10/1861, XIX, 133 (Box 16)
    - 06/11/1861, XIX, 134 (Box 16)
    - 06/12/1861, XIX, 135 (Box 16)
    - 06/13/1861, XIX, 135 (Box 16)
    - 06/15/1861. XIX, 136 (Box 16)
    - 06/17/1861, XIX, 137 (Box 16)
    - 06/18/1861, XIX, 138 (Box 16)
    - 06/19/1861, XIX, 139 (Box 16)
    - 06/20/1861, XIX, 140 (Box 16)
    - 06/21/1861, XIX, 141 (Box 16)
    - 06/22/1861, XIX, 142 (Box 16)
    - 07/19/1861, XX, 17 (Box 16)
    - 07/20/1861, XX, 18 (Box 16)
    - 07/22/1861, XX, 19 (Box 16)
    - 07/23/1861, XX, 20 (Box 16)
    - 07/24/1861, XX, 21 (Box 16)
    - 02/1862, XXI, 29 (Box 16)
    - 05/31/1861, XIX, 125 (Box 11)
    - 10/26/1875, XLVIII, 102 (Box 11)
    - 02/06/1878, LIII, 32 (Box 11)
    - 02/24/1879, LV, 47 (Box 11)
    - 02/26/1879, LV, 49 (Box 11)
    - 02/27/1879, LV, 50 (Box 11)
    - 03/06/1879, LV, 56 (Box 11)
    - 07/12/1882, LXII, 10 (Box 11)
    - 11/03/1883, LXIV, 107 (Box 11)
    - 10/29/1875, 19, 44 (Box 11)
    - 07/12/1878, XXII, 28 (Box 11)
  - Daily Richmond Examiner, Richmond, VA
    - 05/10/1866, I, 119
  - Evening Leader (The), Richmond and Manchester, VA
    - 11/01/1899, 3, 912
    - 05/17/1901, 5, 123
    - 05/18/1901, 5, 124
    - 06/27/1901, 5, 158
  - Religious Herald, Richmond, VA
    - 03/21/1895, LXVIII, 12
  - Republic (The), Richmond, VA
    - 12/06/1865, 2, 23
  - Richmond Dispatch (The), Richmond, VA
    - 07/29/1885
    - 10/02/1889
    - 10/23/1889
    - 11/06/1889
    - 12/06/1889
    - 12/08/1889
    - 05/10/1890
    - 08/07/1891
    - 11/15/1896
    - 12/06/1896
    - 06/19/1901
    - 07/05/1901
    - 07/11/1901
    - 07/14/1901
    - 07/16/1901
    - 07/17/1901
    - 07/18/1901
    - 07/19/1901
    - 07/23/1901
    - 07/24/1901
    - 07/27/1901
    - 07/30/1901
    - 07/31/1901
    - 08/01/1901
    - 08/02/1901
    - 08/03/1901
    - 08/06/1901
    - 08/07/1901
    - 08/08/1901
    - 08/10/1901
    - 08/11/1901
    - 08/13/1901
    - 08/16/1901
    - 08/24/1901
    - 08/27/1901
    - 08/28/1901
    - 08/29/1901
    - 08/31/1901
    - 09/03/1901
    - 09/04/1901
    - 09/05/1901
    - 09/06/1901
    - 09/07/1901
    - 09/08/1901
    - 09/11/1901
    - 09/12/1901
    - 09/14/1901
    - 09/15/1901
    - 09/15/1901
    - 09/17/1901
    - 12/24/1901
  - Richmond Enquirer (The), Richmond, VA
    - 04/13/1861, LVII, 100
    - 04/16/1861, LVII, 102
    - 04/25/1861, LVII, 106
    - 04/30/1861, LVII, 107
    - 05/10/1861, LVIII, 2
    - 05/14/1861, LVIII, 3
    - 05/24/1861, LVIII, 6
    - 05/31/1861, LVIII, 8
    - 06/04/1861, LVIII, 9
    - 06/19/1861, LVIII, 12
    - 06/20/1861, LVIII, 14
    - 06/25/1861, LVIII, 16
    - 07/04/1861, LVIII, 19
    - 07/11/1861, LVIII, 21
    - 07/19/1861, LVIII, 24
    - 07/26/1861, LVIII, 26
    - 07/30/1861, LVIII, 27
    - 08/02/1861, LVIII, 28
    - 08/13/1861, LVIII, 31
    - 08/16/1861, LVIII, 32
    - 08/30/1861, LVIII, 36
    - 09/06/1861, LVIII, 38
    - 09/17/1861, LVIII, 41
    - 09/20/1861, LVIII, 42
    - 09/24/1861, LVIII, 25
    - 10/04/1861, LVIII, 28
    - 02/20/1874, L, 15
    - 01/08/1862, VII, 40
  - Richmond Journal (The), Richmond and Manchester, VA
    - 08/12/1961
  - Richmond Mercury (The), Richmond, VA
    - 1972/09/13, 1, 1 (Box 13)
    - 1972/09/20, 1, 2 (Box 13)
    - 1972/09/27, 1, 3 (Box 13)
    - 1972/10/04, 1, 4 (Box 13)
    - 1972/10/11, 1, 5 (Box 13)
    - 1972/10/10, 1, 6 (Box 13)
    - 1972/10/25, 1, 7 (Box 13)
    - 1972/11/01, 1, 8 (Box 13)
    - 1972/11/08, 1, 9 (Box 13)
    - 1972/11/15, 1, 10 (Box 13)
    - 1972/11/22, 1, 11 (Box 13)
    - 1972/11/29, 1, 12 (Box 13)
    - 1972/12/06, 1, 13 (Box 13)
    - 1972/12/13, 1, 14 (Box 13)
    - 1972/12/20, 1, 15 (Box 13)
    - 1972/12/27, 1, 16 (Box 13)
    - 1973/01/03, 1, 17 (Box 13)
    - 1973/01/10, 1, 18 (Box 13)
    - 1973/01/17, 1, 19 (Box 13)
    - 1973/01/24, 1, 20 (Box 13)
    - 1973/01/31, 1, 21 (Box 13)
    - 1973/02/07, 1, 22 (Box 13)
    - 1973/02/14, 1, 23 (Box 13)
    - 1973/02/21, 1, 24 (Box 13)
    - 1973/02/28, 1, 25 (Box 13)
    - 1973/03/07, 1, 26 (Box 13)
    - 1973/03/14, 1, 27 (Box 13)
    - 1973/03/21, 1, 28 (Box 13)
    - 1973/03/28, 1, 29 (Box 13)
    - 1973/04/04, 1, 30 (Box 13)
    - 1973/04/11, 1, 31 (Box 13)
    - 1973/04/18, 1, 32 (Box 13)
    - 1973/04/25, 1, 33 (Box 13)
    - 1973/05/02, 1, 34 (Box 13)
    - 1973/05/09, 1, 35 (Box 13)
    - 1973/05/16, 1, 36 (Box 13)
    - 1973/05/23, 1, 37 (Box 13)
    - 1973/05/30, 1, 38 (Box 13)
    - 1973/06/06, 1, 39 (Box 13)
    - 1973/06/13, 1, 40 (Box 13)
    - 1973/06/20, 1, 41 (Box 13)
    - 1973/06/27, 1, 42 (Box 13)
    - 1973/07/04, 1, 43 (Box 13)
    - 1973/07/11, 1, 44 (Box 13)
    - 1973/07/18, 1, 45 (Box 13)
    - 1973/07/25, 1, 46 (Box 13)
    - 1973/08/01, 1, 47 (Box 13)
    - 1973/08/08, 1, 48 (Box 13)
    - 1973/08/15, 1, 49 (Box 13)
    - 1973/08/22, 1, 50 (Box 13)
    - 1973/08/28, 1, 51 (Box 13)
    - 1973/09/05, 1, 52 (Box 13)
    - 1973/09/12, 2, 1 (Box 13)
    - 1973/09/19, 2, 2 (Box 13)
    - 1973/09/26, 2, 3 (Box 13)
    - 1973/10/03, 2, 4 (Box 14)
    - 1973/10/10, 2, 5 (Box 14)
    - 1973/10/17, 2, 6 (Box 14)
    - 1973/10/24, 2, 7 (Box 14)
    - 1973/10/31, 2, 8 (Box 14)
    - 1973/11/07, 2, 9 (Box 14)
    - 1973/11/14, 2, 10 (Box 14)
    - 1973/11/28, 2, 12 (Box 14)
    - 1973/12/26, 2, 16 (Box 14)
    - 1974/02/06, 2, 22 (Box 14)
    - 1974/02/13, 2, 23 (Box 14)
    - 1974/02/27, 2, 25 (Box 14)
    - 1974/03/13, 2, 27 (Box 14)
    - 1974/03/20, 2, 28 (Box 14)
    - 1974/03/27, 2, 29 (Box 14)
    - 1974/04/03, 2, 30 (Box 14)
    - 1974/04/10, 2, 31 (Box 14)
    - 1974/04/17, 2, 32 (Box 14)
    - 1974/04/24, 2, 33 (Box 14)
    - 1974/05/01, 2, 34 (Box 14)
    - 1974/05/08, 2, 35 (Box 14)
    - 1974/05/15, 2, 36 (Box 14)
    - 1974/05/22, 2, 37 (Box 14)
    - 1974/05/296, 2, 38 (Box 14)
    - 1974/06/05, 2, 39 (Box 14)
    - 1974/06/12, 2, 40 (Box 14)
    - 1974/06/19, 2, 41 (Box 14)
    - 1974/06/26, 2, 42 (Box 14)
    - 1974/07/03, 2, 43 (Box 14)
    - 1974/07/10, 2, 44 (Box 14)
    - 1974/07/17, 2, 45 (Box 14)
    - 1974/07/24, 2, 46 (Box 14)
    - 1974/07/31, 2, 47 (Box 14)
    - 1974/08/07, 2, 48 (Box 14)
    - 1974/08/14, 2, 49 (Box 14)
    - 1974/08/21, 2, 50 (Box 14)
    - 1974/08/28, 2, 51 (Box 14)
    - 1974/09/04, 2, 52 (Box 14)
    - 1974/09/11, 3, 1 (Box 14)
    - 1974/09/18, 3, 2 (Box 14)
    - 1974/09/25, 3, 3 (Box 14)
    - 1974/10/02, 3, 4 (Box 14)
    - 1974/10/09, 3, 5 (Box 14)
    - 1974/10/16, 3, 6 (Box 14)
    - 1974/10/30, 3, 8 (Box 14)
    - 1974/11/06, 3, 9 (Box 14)
    - 1974/11/20, 3, 11 (Box 14)
    - 1974/11/27, 3, 12 (Box 14)
    - 1974/12/04, 3, 13 (Box 14)
    - 1974/12/11, 3, 14 (Box 14)
    - 1974/12/18, 3, 15 (Box 14)
    - 1974/12/25, 3, 16 (Box 14)
  - Richmond News (The), Richmond, VA
    - 02/23/1901, 31
    - 05/18/1901, 2, 191
    - 06/21/1901, 2, 220
    - 09/07/1901, II, 286
    - 10/17/1901, III, 12
  - Richmond News Leader (The), Richmond, VA
    - 04/03/1915
    - 09/08/1937
  - Richmond Whig and Advertiser (The), Richmond, VA
    - 12/16/1881, 58, 98
    - 05/16/1864
    - 08/10/1875, 52, 189
    - 08/08/1877, 44, 168
    - 01/28/1878, 55, 24
    - 02/06/1878, 55, 32
    - 07/09/1880, 57, 33
    - 12/10/1880, 57, 50
    - 01/07/1881, 58, 1
    - 01/14/1881, 58, 2
    - 10/16/1885, 62, 42
  - Richmond Whig and Public Advertiser, Richmond, VA
    - 07/26/1861, 38, 60
  - Semi-Weekly Dispatch (The) (Richmond Dispatch), Richmond, VA
    - 10/27/1885
    - 02/16/1886
  - Sentinel (The), Richmond, VA
    - 04/01/1864
  - State (The), Richmond, VA
    - 08/09/1877, II, 122
    - 08/05/1881, VI, 119
    - 09/13/1889, XIV, 152
    - 02/18/1896
    - 08/09/1897
  - Times (The), Richmond, VA
    - 12/26/1897, 12, 279
    - 06/25/1899
    - 05/12/1901, 16, 104
    - 07/05/1901, 16, 124
    - 07/12/1901, 16, 130
    - 07/13/1901, 16, 131
    - 07/14/1901, 16, 132
    - 07/19/1901, 16, 136
    - 07/21/1901
    - 07/23/1901, 16, 139
    - 07/24/1901, 16, 140
    - 07/26/1901, 16, 142
    - 07/28/1901, 16, 146
    - 08/01/1901, 16, 147
    - 08/03/1901, 16, 149
    - 08/04/1901, 16, 159
    - 08/06/1901, 16, 151
    - 08/10/1901, 16, 155
    - 08/11/1901, 16, 156
    - 08/13/1901, 16, 157
    - 08/16/1901, 16, 161
    - 08/20/1901, 16, 164
    - 09/07/1901, 16, 181
    - 09/26/1901, 16, 198
  - Times-Dispatch (The), Richmond, VA
    - 01/17/1904
    - 02/17/1907
    - 10/19/1908
    - 10/21/1908
    - 03/19/1972
- Box 12: Roanoke-Wytheville, Virginia (General) (Box 12)
  - Clinch Valley News, Tazewell C. H., VA
    - 03/08/1878, 7, 42
    - 08/19/1881, 5, 47
    - 11/11/1881, 5, 48
  - Evening Star (The), Winchester, VA
    - 02/16/1907, XI, 325
  - Lotus-Eaters of 1940 (The) (Reprint from the Louisville Courier-Journal-3 pages), VA
    - 01/00/1900
  - Roanoke Times (The), Roanoke, VA
    - 08/10/1897, XVIII, 102
    - 05/21/1901, XXVIII, 121
    - 06/18/1901, XXVIII, 144
    - 03/24/1907, XLI, 72
    - 05/08/1945, CXVII, 128
    - 08/15/1945, 118, 46
  - Roanoke Times-Progress Editions (The), Roanoke, VA
    - 02/04/1962, 12
    - 01/13/1962, 13
  - Roanoke Times-Virginia Tech Centennial (The), Roanoke, VA
    - 03/19/1972
  - Roanoke Times-World-News (The), Roanoke, VA
    - 10/22/1965
    - 05/12/1968
  - Roanoke Times & World News (The), Roanoke, VA
    - 04/18/1982
    - 04/25/1982
    - 05/07/1945, 85, 109
  - Staunton Daily News, Staunton, VA
    - 01/19/1899, 8
  - Staunton Dispatch and News, Staunton, VA
    - 02/28/1908, 17, 49
  - Strasburg News (The), VA
    - 08/11/1899
  - Strikes (List-5 pages), VA
    - 12/09/1940-02/21/1940
  - Tidewater Democrat (The), Tappahanock, VA
    - 08/10/1897, I, 46
  - Times-Register (The), Salem, VA
    - 05/27/1938, 83, 42
  - Those Crippling Strikes from the Los Angelos Times (1 page), VA
    - 01/00/1900
  - Virginia Gazette-Jamestown Festival Edition (The), Williamsburg, VA
    - 6/28/1957
  - Virginia Southwest Enterprise, Wytheville, VA
    - 01/29/1873, III, 33
    - 02/08/1873, III, 56
    - 05/10/1873, III, 82
    - 07/04/1875, V, 99
    - 07/21/1881, XI, 100
    - 11/10/1881, XI, 113
    - 03/01/1882, XII, 39
  - Weekly Religious Herald (The), Seddon, VA
    - 04/07/1874, II, 21